

CONTACT

+48 452 202 441

✓ krystinabutko@gmail.com

Krakow, Poland

EDUCATION

2003 - 2006

Belorussian State College of Telecommunications

Telecommunications Network
Technician (Software)

SKILLS

- PHP (Symfony, Laravel, CMS)
- Docker
- PHPUnit
- Design Patterns
- JS (Vue.js)
- SQL (MySQL, MariaDB)
- RabbitMQ
- Linux (Ubuntu)
- Git (GitLab, Bitbucket)
- CI/CD
- Jira
- SCRAM
- HTML, CSS

LANGUAGES

- English (B2)
- Polish (A2)

CHRISTINA ASIPENKA

PHP DEVELOPER

PROFILE

PHP developer with 4+ years of experience in web development. Have a solid knowledge of Symfony and Laravel frameworks, JavaScript, SQL.

I'm focused on writing clean and maintainable code using design patterns, good architecture and SOLID principles. I always apply a creative approach to offer the best solutions for every project to customers. I am a perfect team player, detail oriented and hard-working developer. Ready to master new technologies and approaches.

WORK EXPERIENCE

AndersenLab

PHP developer

Responsibilities

 Developed a multilingual banking application that provided users with an access to their accounts and allowed them to make deposits, review and pay their loans and bills, set up auto payments, check monthly statements

10.2022 - 03.2024

- Test coverage, code refactoring and debugging
- Connecting microservices using RabbitMQ

Technologies and tools

PHP, Symfony, MySQL, MariaDB, Docker, RabbitMQ, PHPUnit, Nginx, GitLab, Jira, Design Patterns

Belorussian State Energy and Gas Supervision 10.2017 - 09.2022
 Lead Software Developer

Responsibilities

- Developed tools that optimized inspectors workflow. The software provided features such as customer registration, reporting incidents; collecting, analysing, transferring of data; pulling and processing reports.
- Analyzed user experience and created documentation based on it.
- Collaborated with other members of the development team to identify and fix the bugs.
- Was a part of the team that maintained the code to make sure that the final product is following the standards for application development architecture.

Technologies and tools

PHP, Laravel, JavaScript, jQuery, VBA, MySQL, MS SQL, PostgreSQL, phpMyAdmin, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, 1C

HOBBIES

- Biking
- Chess
- Reading books

E-Commerce websites

01.2017 - 10.2017

Full-stack developer

- Developed websites for online stores with user friendly interface and features that provided better shopping experience.
- Developed plugins for CMS.
- Worked on improving existing functionality.
- Performed code debugging and participated in the upgrading processes.

Technologies and tools

PHP, JavaScript, jQuery, MySQL, Apache, phpMyAdmin, HTML, CSS, OpenCart, WordPress, Drupal, Joomla, Bootstrap

Open Joint Stock Company "Vitebsk Factory of 08.2006 - 09.2016 Electrical Tools"

Software Developer

- Developed a new software for the accounting department. Was a part of the team that was working on a set of programs for payroll, keeping track of stationery, calculating sales profits and stock balances.
- Maintained the old software for the accounting team and participated on developing new software for the HR department.
- Worked on improving user experience by testing software modules.
- Collected tickets and bug reports from the users, performed debugging and created user documentation.

Technologies and tools

Clipper, VBA, DBF, Visual Fox Pro, PHP, JS, HTML, CSS